Guide to the Alumni Board, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Alumni Board, Yale University, records
1950-1960
RU 193
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(6 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, and reports documenting the activities and operations of the Yale University Alumni Board. Topics include alumni fund convocations, football games, cocktail parties, reunions, and finances.
Yale University. Alumni Board
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-C-1 (YRG 8-C-1), Records of organizations open to all Yale alumni.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, and reports documenting the activities and operations of the Yale University Alumni Board. Topics include alumni fund convocations, football games, cocktail parties, reunions, and finances.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.; Yale University. Alumni Board
- Records, 1950-1960; Accession 1965-A-004
  - Alumni Fund Convocations, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Fund Convocations, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Fund Convocations 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of America University Presses 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bretton Woods Conference - American Alumni Council, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chaplains Convocation 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cocktail parties - football weekends 1957-58, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, financial records, lists, programs
    - 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Development Committee Convocation, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Development Cornittee meeting, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Development Convocation, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee-on Enrollment and Scholarships Convocation, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fall functions, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fall functions, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fall functions, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fall functions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fall functions, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Football games
    - Columbia, Colgate, Dartmouth, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Harvard, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Harvard Luncheon, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Cornell, Dartmouth, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Princeton, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Brown, Dartmouth, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Harvard, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Harvard - cocktail parties and luncheon, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dartmouth, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Brown, Cornell, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Princeton, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Prince ton, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Princeton, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Princeton - cocktail parties, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Football tents, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Football tents, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ivy League Coaches, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Summer Conferences, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - University Development Convocations, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - World Council of Churches Convocation, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Chairman's report from and copy of speech by A. W. Griswold at Alumni Board Convocation, 1952 October; Accession 1996-A-025
  - Chairman's report from and copy of speech by A. W. Griswold at Alumni Board Convocation, 1952 October (Box 1)